[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "But what do you think of him personally?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "him", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, I don't -- I don't actually know him.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "actually", "know", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "When you see the charge of potential racism in the Herman Cain case, people saying that people are only going after him because he's a black conservative, do you think that holds any merit?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "charge", "of", "potential", "racism", "in", "the", "Herman", "Cain", "case", ",", "people", "saying", "that", "people", "are", "only", "going", "after", "him", "because", "he", "'s", "a", "black", "conservative", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "holds", "any", "merit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, I actually don't like playing the race card on either side.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "actually", "do", "n't", "like", "playing", "the", "race", "card", "on", "either", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "What can you read into this from your experience?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "read", "into", "this", "from", "your", "experience", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, I don't think you can read anything in at this point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "can", "read", "anything", "in", "at", "this", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Which of the candidates do you find yourself agreeing with most on their policy statements?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "of", "the", "candidates", "do", "you", "find", "yourself", "agreeing", "with", "most", "on", "their", "policy", "statements", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Do you think maybe you should throw your hat in the ring, albeit, belatedly?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "maybe", "you", "should", "throw", "your", "hat", "in", "the", "ring", ",", "albeit", ",", "belatedly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "No, I certainly don't get itchy fingers about throwing my own hat in the ring.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "certainly", "do", "n't", "get", "itchy", "fingers", "about", "throwing", "my", "own", "hat", "in", "the", "ring", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "And so, the important thing to look for in candidates is what do they stand for, what are their principles, do they understand the unique character of the United States, and its unique role in the world?", "question_tokens": ["And", "so", ",", "the", "important", "thing", "to", "look", "for", "in", "candidates", "is", "what", "do", "they", "stand", "for", ",", "what", "are", "their", "principles", ",", "do", "they", "understand", "the", "unique", "character", "of", "the", "United", "States", ",", "and", "its", "unique", "role", "in", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Let's turn to your book.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "turn", "to", "your", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "What did you conclude about that period in your life?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "conclude", "about", "that", "period", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Well, first of all, there was the relief that I finally finished the writing, which, as you know, can be quite trying.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "there", "was", "the", "relief", "that", "I", "finally", "finished", "the", "writing", ",", "which", ",", "as", "you", "know", ",", "can", "be", "quite", "trying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "How have I done there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "I", "done", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Let's start over.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "start", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Object of affection?", "question_tokens": ["Object", "of", "affection", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "What did you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Well, revolutions are not pretty, and there are any number of circumstances in which the tyrant who stays too long and refuses to leave and when fear breaks down, and on behalf of his people, and the tables are turned, those ends are often very violent.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "revolutions", "are", "not", "pretty", ",", "and", "there", "are", "any", "number", "of", "circumstances", "in", "which", "the", "tyrant", "who", "stays", "too", "long", "and", "refuses", "to", "leave", "and", "when", "fear", "breaks", "down", ",", "and", "on", "behalf", "of", "his", "people", ",", "and", "the", "tables", "are", "turned", ",", "those", "ends", "are", "often", "very", "violent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Do you look at what's happened to Barack and Gadhafi, and slightly regret the way you helped the administration go about Iraq?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "look", "at", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "Barack", "and", "Gadhafi", ",", "and", "slightly", "regret", "the", "way", "you", "helped", "the", "administration", "go", "about", "Iraq", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Well, the circumstances were fundamentally different, and the times were fundamentally different.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "circumstances", "were", "fundamentally", "different", ",", "and", "the", "times", "were", "fundamentally", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["Barack", "Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "Is that -- is that a total lifetime pass, or could you see yourself tempted back?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "--", "is", "that", "a", "total", "lifetime", "pass", ",", "or", "could", "you", "see", "yourself", "tempted", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "I'm really a policy person.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "really", "a", "policy", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "You're not entirely ruling it out?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "entirely", "ruling", "it", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Piers, that's a no.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["State Department"]}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ":", "CD", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Who was the first person you told when you heard the news?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "was", "the", "first", "person", "you", "told", "when", "you", "heard", "the", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Well, I actually had a couple of people with me, traveling with me -- one of whom had worked with me at the State Department.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "actually", "had", "a", "couple", "of", "people", "with", "me", ",", "traveling", "with", "me", "--", "one", "of", "whom", "had", "worked", "with", "me", "at", "the", "State", "Department", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "So, I guess mixed feelings?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "I", "guess", "mixed", "feelings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, of course, it was a wonderful experience, and it was a very high honor, as I said.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", ",", "it", "was", "a", "wonderful", "experience", ",", "and", "it", "was", "a", "very", "high", "honor", ",", "as", "I", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["June of 2005"], "PERSON": ["Bush"], "LOCATION": ["United States of America", "Middle East", "Cairo"]}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "WDT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "And very quickly, if I was to pin you down and say your biggest triumph in the eight years and your biggest regret, what would you say?", "question_tokens": ["And", "very", "quickly", ",", "if", "I", "was", "to", "pin", "you", "down", "and", "say", "your", "biggest", "triumph", "in", "the", "eight", "years", "and", "your", "biggest", "regret", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "Well, clearly, associating the United States of America firmly with the freedom agenda in the Middle East after 60 years of trying to trade democracy for stability and getting neither, I'm very proud of that speech in Cairo in June of 2005 that set a different tone based on President Bush's second inaugural.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "clearly", ",", "associating", "the", "United", "States", "of", "America", "firmly", "with", "the", "freedom", "agenda", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "after", "60", "years", "of", "trying", "to", "trade", "democracy", "for", "stability", "and", "getting", "neither", ",", "I", "'m", "very", "proud", "of", "that", "speech", "in", "Cairo", "in", "June", "of", "2005", "that", "set", "a", "different", "tone", "based", "on", "President", "Bush", "'s", "second", "inaugural", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["ACKERMAN"]}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Is that in a nutshell where we are with this?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "in", "a", "nutshell", "where", "we", "are", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "LLIOT ACKERMAN, COO, AMERICANS ELECT: I think you hit it right on the head.", "answer_tokens": ["LLIOT", "ACKERMAN", ",", "COO", ",", "AMERICANS", "ELECT", ":", "I", "think", "you", "hit", "it", "right", "on", "the", "head", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Are you going to end up come election with all the states allowing this or not?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "end", "up", "come", "election", "with", "all", "the", "states", "allowing", "this", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Coming to your show today, it's already happening.", "answer_tokens": ["Coming", "to", "your", "show", "today", ",", "it", "'s", "already", "happening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NNPS", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Do you need to have that kind of powerful figurehead for this to really work?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "need", "to", "have", "that", "kind", "of", "powerful", "figurehead", "for", "this", "to", "really", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "What's so interesting about it the Americans Elect platform gives the American people the opportunity to select leaders from business, from government, people who have expressed leadership roughly the previous 44 presidents have.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "'s", "so", "interesting", "about", "it", "the", "Americans", "Elect", "platform", "gives", "the", "American", "people", "the", "opportunity", "to", "select", "leaders", "from", "business", ",", "from", "government", ",", "people", "who", "have", "expressed", "leadership", "roughly", "the", "previous", "44", "presidents", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Who's funding al this?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "funding", "al", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, we've had over 3,000 donors up until this point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'ve", "had", "over", "3,000", "donors", "up", "until", "this", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "If they're watching us and if they want to get involved in your caper, as it is at the moment, may become a more serious caper, where do they go?", "question_tokens": ["If", "they", "'re", "watching", "us", "and", "if", "they", "want", "to", "get", "involved", "in", "your", "caper", ",", "as", "it", "is", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "may", "become", "a", "more", "serious", "caper", ",", "where", "do", "they", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "CKERMAN: Well, it's already a serious caper.", "answer_tokens": ["CKERMAN", ":", "Well", ",", "it", "'s", "already", "a", "serious", "caper", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "I mea, he's sort of a part of American history, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mea", ",", "he", "'s", "sort", "of", "a", "part", "of", "American", "history", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "What was he like when the door closed?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "when", "the", "door", "closed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "AYNE: He was -- he was very similar in a lot of ways.", "answer_tokens": ["AYNE", ":", "He", "was", "--", "he", "was", "very", "similar", "in", "a", "lot", "of", "ways", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Was he actually any good with a gun?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "actually", "any", "good", "with", "a", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "He was very good with a gun.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "very", "good", "with", "a", "gun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "What were your recollections of that time in your life?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "your", "recollections", "of", "that", "time", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "AYNE: You know, it was -- it's always a strange time for young men when they're at that age.", "answer_tokens": ["AYNE", ":", "You", "know", ",", "it", "was", "--", "it", "'s", "always", "a", "strange", "time", "for", "young", "men", "when", "they", "'re", "at", "that", "age", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "What's the biggest misconception, do you think, of your father?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "biggest", "misconception", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "of", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "I don't know if there is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "there", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "What would he have made of the modern political state and financial state of the America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "he", "have", "made", "of", "the", "modern", "political", "state", "and", "financial", "state", "of", "the", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Piers, we're all shaking our heads.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "we", "'re", "all", "shaking", "our", "heads", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Imagine he would have been pretty furious, wouldn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Imagine", "he", "would", "have", "been", "pretty", "furious", ",", "would", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "He'd be upset.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'d", "be", "upset", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "What's been your favorite movie of your father's -- if you could actually watch one again?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "your", "favorite", "movie", "of", "your", "father", "'s", "--", "if", "you", "could", "actually", "watch", "one", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Well, mine changes all the time, because, you know, I'm 49 now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "mine", "changes", "all", "the", "time", ",", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "49", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Wayne"]}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "It is interesting, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "interesting", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Well, I don't know if there is another actor who's had the opportunity to, you know, create a space for themselves like John Wayne was able to.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "there", "is", "another", "actor", "who", "'s", "had", "the", "opportunity", "to", ",", "you", "know", ",", "create", "a", "space", "for", "themselves", "like", "John", "Wayne", "was", "able", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "Can you do a John Wayne?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "do", "a", "John", "Wayne", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "AYNE: No, I can't.", "answer_tokens": ["AYNE", ":", "No", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Wayne"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "You never tried it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "tried", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Well, I don't know if I would do it on national television.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "would", "do", "it", "on", "national", "television", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Which will it be?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "will", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "I call that bold talk for a one-eyed fat man.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "call", "that", "bold", "talk", "for", "a", "one-eyed", "fat", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Winning the Oscar for best actor?", "question_tokens": ["Winning", "the", "Oscar", "for", "best", "actor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Yes, because it's the ultimate in the profession, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "the", "ultimate", "in", "the", "profession", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "A well- traveled man, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["A", "well-", "traveled", "man", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Always on the move.", "answer_tokens": ["Always", "on", "the", "move", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congressional Gold Medal"]}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "What is this one?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "this", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "This is the Congressional Gold Medal and it's the highest civilian award.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "Congressional", "Gold", "Medal", "and", "it", "'s", "the", "highest", "civilian", "award", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNPS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Which movie is that from?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "movie", "is", "that", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "This is from the \"Green Berets.\"", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "from", "the", "``", "Green", "Berets", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Who were people paying this kind of money?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "were", "people", "paying", "this", "kind", "of", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "I have my suspicions about the \"Green Beret.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "my", "suspicions", "about", "the", "``", "Green", "Beret", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Special Forces", "Special Forces"]}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "WP", "VBD", "RP", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "What are they?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Well, there was an individual who came out who is a former Special Forces, and he had done well, and I have a feeling that he may have bought that to put it in one of the Special Forces museums.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "was", "an", "individual", "who", "came", "out", "who", "is", "a", "former", "Special", "Forces", ",", "and", "he", "had", "done", "well", ",", "and", "I", "have", "a", "feeling", "that", "he", "may", "have", "bought", "that", "to", "put", "it", "in", "one", "of", "the", "Special", "Forces", "museums", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "``", "PRP", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Which movie is that from?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "movie", "is", "that", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "\"Horse Soldiers,\" \"She Wore a Yellow Ribbon\" and \"The Undefeated (ph).\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Horse", "Soldiers", ",", "''", "``", "She", "Wore", "a", "Yellow", "Ribbon", "''", "and", "``", "The", "Undefeated", "(", "ph", ")", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBP", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "What size?", "question_tokens": ["What", "size", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Well, these are custom made.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "these", "are", "custom", "made", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]